John Rock

Web Developer

Passionate Web Developer with 3+ years of professional experience in front-end development.

My goal is to be a part of a dynamic work environment where I can utilize my knowledge and skills to assist with the growth of the organization and myself.

(570) 507-4498 johnmrock.jr@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/john-rock johnrock.me

EXPERIENCE

Lead Developer | Net Driven

August 2019 - Present

- Manage and train offshore developers.
- Review and delegate daily tasks in work queue.
- Create process documentation.
- Debug and deploy fixes for errors on platform.
- Spearheaded project to implement the use of the CSS preprocessor SCSS on platform by using a Gulp.js workflow.
- Accelerated development by creating a library of commonly used assets.
- Create custom reports using Salesforce to refine workflow.

Front-End Developer | Net Driven

July 2016 - August 2019

- Develop websites on the DotNetNuke platform for the automotive industry.
- Work with HTML, CSS, and jQuery to convert wireframes into fully functioning websites.
- Manage all national tire rebates to ensure assets are created and rebates are set to start and expire on correct date.
- Design graphics for websites using Adobe Creative Suite.

EDUCATION

Keystone College | La Plume, PA

August 2014 - July 2016

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

Johnson College of Technology | Scranton, PA

August 2012 - May 2014

Associate in Computer Information Technology

SKILLS

Project Management Research and Development Troubleshooting Employee Training

LANGUAGES

HTML

CSS / SCSS

JavaScript

GraphQL jQuery Markdown MySQL PHP Node.js React

TOOLS

Adobe Creative Suite
DotNetNuke
Figma
GatsbyJs
G Suite
Git
Gulp.js
Netlify
REST API
Salesforce
Visual Studio Code
Wordpress